

# Cody Tripp

## **Professional Summary**

Goal-oriented Web Developer with strong commitment to collaboration and solutions-oriented problem-solving. Use various web design software to develop customer-focused websites and designs. Committed to high standards of web design, user experience, usability and speed for multiple types of end-users. Successful at maintaining customer satisfaction through effective customer support.

# Work History

### Cheesecake Factory - Line Cook

Mesa, AZ

11/2019 - Current

- Prepared food items to meet recipes, portioning, cooking and waste control guidelines.
- Cleaned counters, food preparation areas and equipment with sanitizing spray to reduce risk of cross-contamination.

### All Aboard Services LLC - Respite Worker

Mesa, AZ

09/2015 - 04/2019

- Maintained safe and hazard-free environments.
- Planned engaging recreational, developmental and entertainment activities.
- Assisted with daily living needs such as personal hygiene.

## Paradise Bakery - Restaurant Busser

Mesa, AZ

10/2013 - 05/2015

- Assisted wait staff with timely food delivery and guest requests.
- Monitored dining room inventory and replenished as necessary.
- Monitored temperature of cases, shelves and storage areas and reported failures to manager.
- Managed customer deliveries and assisted with carrying out orders to promote maximum satisfaction.
- Ensured exceptional guest experiences through attentive service.

codydeantripp@gmail.com (480) 528-8370 Mesa, AZ 85212

### Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- JQuery

### Education

05/2016

**Desert Ridge High School High School Diploma** 

### **Certifications**

Full Stack Web Development - University of Arizona